As I expected, Aria really is the strongest of all the participants.

At the same time, Rio felt a keen sense of Aria’s abilities firsthand. Liselotte’s other attendants, Cosette and Natalie, had been at an even level with Vanessa and Louise, but Aria’s swordsmanship was closer to Alfred’s, the King’s Sword. She had more than enough talent to be working as the head attendant of a duke’s daughter.

Aria would need to face Aishia for a worthwhile match. Though Sara and Alma may put up a good fight if they team up together, Rio thought as he fended off Aria’s attacks. It’d be a different matter if spirit arts were allowed, but Sara and Alma wouldn’t be able to win under the same conditions alone. If he were to hold a series of battles to rank the participants with the exception of Aishia and himself, Aria would come out as the decisive winner, followed by Sara and Alma. Below them would be Natalie, Cosette, Vanessa, and Louise. After that would be the other knights.

Incidentally, when Satsuki tried to enhance her physical abilities, she found the enhancements of her Divine Arms were activated even without manifesting the weapon. This meant she couldn’t fight under the same conditions as the other participants, so she couldn’t be ranked, but if Rio were to rank them with Divine Arms, spirit arts, and enchanted swords allowed, she’d probably rank near the top.

He’d sparred with her multiple times since living in the castle mansion, and she had shown impressive growth in a short time. However...

She really is formidable...

Even then, Satsuki would have a hard time against Aria. That was how superior Aria’s abilities were. Not only was every one of her movements clean and efficient, she had a good sense of technique to make her actions hard to predict.

The skirt she’s wearing makes it hard to measure the distance. It may be a little unusual to see an attendant fighting in her work uniform, but considering how she was going to use a weapon, it was probably a reasonable combat outfit. Though it’s easier to grab at when one is fighting with their fists...

For example, a trained knight would be able to see through their opponents based on their body’s movements, but what was most vital was the visual information received from watching the feet, such as the timing of steps and kicks. That’s why it was normal to purposefully use the body’s movements as feints or learn techniques to hide them as much as possible, but hiding the feet with a long skirt was another clever method. Rio also used a long coat when he usually fought to make his feet harder to see, but a skirt could cover a greater area.

That being said, Cosette and Natalie were similarly wearing skirts. The reason why Rio found Aria harder to fight than them was simply because she had better skills. She had perfectly mastered techniques to conceal her movements on top of hiding her feet with her skirt, so even though her physical abilities weren’t any different from the others, it gave the illusion that her speed was greater. On top of that, she was constantly making the best move with the fastest speed.

However, Rio was keeping up with her movements perfectly, so their match was turning out to be much more advanced than the others. Rio had only moved a few meters while fighting the others, but now he was being forced to move much farther to deal with Aria’s attacks. The observers of their match all had their eyes opened wide.

Those who were the most surprised were the ones seeing Aria fight for the first time—in particular, the knights. They looked on, dumbfounded.

“How intense...” Vanessa muttered, watching Aria.

“I’ve heard rumors that Lady Liselotte’s head attendant is skilled, but this is something else,” Louise replied.

A short distance away, Cosette overheard their conversation and mumbled, “Sir Haruto is also amazing for being able to keep up with her fierce attacks so perfectly. I wouldn’t last more than a few seconds...”

Liselotte’s attendants all trained every day, and the one that oversaw them was Aria. Their menu included regularly facing her in a one-on-one match, which the attendants all feared as the training from hell.

“Hey, you guys. Who is she?” Vanessa asked Natalie and Cosette.

“She’s our head attendant. Her name’s Aria,” Cosette answered with a shrug.

“I heard that during her self-introduction... But what kind of history does she have? It seems like she’s learned the sword style of the Beltrum Kingdom,” Vanessa continued.

Since she also used the Beltrum style of swordsmanship, she had noticed that similarity.

“Hmm... Well, it’s not like it’s a secret, so I guess it should be fine to say. She was born to a viscount family of Beltrum.”

Aria had mentioned it herself last time she met a knight of the Beltrum Kingdom.

“So she’s a viscount’s daughter from our kingdom? Why is she serving a duke’s daughter in Galarc...?”

Did that mean she was employed as a servant? Anyone born to a viscount family with sword skills like that would normally join the knights—and there was no doubt she’d achieve great success there. It wouldn’t be strange for her to be assigned to royalty like Christina or Flora. Vanessa looked like she wanted to recruit her.

“I’m afraid that’s a more private question, so please ask Aria herself. She’s not that bothered by it, so I doubt she’ll refuse to answer, but it’s her own matter to discuss.”

“Hmm, I see... No, I’m sorry for troubling you.” Vanessa sensed the change in the atmosphere and refrained from pressing the issue. However, she still felt regretful that their kingdom had lost such a talented person and bit down on her lip in frustration.

Meanwhile, Rio switched from defense to offense. He pursued the trajectory of Aria’s sword, swinging his sword across in the same direction to counterstrike. Aria used the force of her swing to leap to the side, evading Rio’s counter by a hair’s breadth.

Rio proceeded to pursue her by closing in. Until now, he’d avoided aggressively attacking the other sparring partners, so the observers started buzzing with noise.

“Guh...”

Aria noticed this as well. Since the other participants hadn’t been actively attacked, she was surprised enough to widen her eyes faintly. But it still wasn’t enough to shake her up—she was able to react to his attacks. With a backstep, she handled his attack, making Rio move forward like he was dancing with his sword.

Rio’s attacks were also splendid, making the observers hold their breath. However, they proceeded to meet swords another ten times.

“Let’s leave it at that.” Rio stopped, calling for an end to the match.

“...Right.” Aria replied with a small breath, lowering her sword.

“Now, let’s return to everyone else.”

“Understood.”

Aria followed Rio as he started walking, watching his back.

What an unbelievable boy... His sword skills are perfect and he fights like a veteran master warrior. It’s terrifying to think he’s only sixteen years old.

She was supposed to be the older one, yet she felt like her sword had more of the passion that could be found in youth. That was the half-exasperated thought that entered Aria’s mind.

An opportunity to face opponents like this doesn’t come by often. I should enjoy it to my fullest while I can.

She smiled happily. After that, Rio, Aria, and Sara, who had been acting as the umpire, returned to where the knights and the others were.

“I’ve gained a good idea of everyone’s abilities after facing all of you. There are a few things I’ve noticed, so I’m going to proceed with the lesson while taking those points into consideration. The goal of today is for everyone here to get stronger, so we’ll hold mock battles in varying numbers to provide a useful learning experience for everyone. I may end up instructing on the spur of the moment, but please bear with me.” Rio explained the direction of the lesson and looked around at everyone. When he bowed his head, the participants all blinked in surprise for a moment.

“Yes, sir!” they all replied energetically.

“Does anyone have any questions?”

“Yes!” Someone’s hand shot into the air.

“What is it, Satsuki?”

“Won’t you spar with me?”

“I’ve been sparring with you ever since I came to this mansion, haven’t I? That’s why I know yours, Sara’s, Alma’s, and Aishia’s abilities already.”

“Hmph...” Satsuki pouted. She had been looking forward to it.

“I can spar with you anytime outside of the lesson, so let’s fight then.”

“Is that a promise?”

“Yes.” Although he shrugged, Rio nodded with a smile.

“Yay! I can’t wait,” Satsuki replied cheerfully.

The knights and attendants watching on sensed how close the two of them were based on that exchange.

“Now, we’ve got no time to waste. Let’s move on to the next menu item.”

The lesson continued for another two hours until lunch, and the participants enjoyed a very fulfilling training session.

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, roughly one hour before the special lesson ended, the girls who had been observing the class, which included Miharu, Celia, Latifa, Orphia, Charlotte, Liselotte, Christina, and Flora, entered the mansion ahead of the others; their goal was to prepare lunch and ready the baths that were just completed yesterday for their guests. The mansion was constructed with royalty in mind, so it was built rather spaciously. Of course, there were baths in the mansion to begin with, but Rio decided to remodel them so that Satsuki could still enjoy herself while he was away from the castle.

The residents of the house (including Satsuki, who practically lived there, and Charlotte) had used the baths yesterday, but Christina, Flora, and Liselotte had yet to give them a try. The three of them expressed their interest in bathing, so it was agreed in advance that they would be brought there once they observed enough of the lesson.

Miharu, Orphia, and Latifa were to prepare lunch while Celia, Charlotte, Liselotte, Christina, and Flora would bathe first. They undressed themselves in the changing room with the help of the attendants, then opened the door connecting to the bathroom.

“Oh my goodness...”

“It’s wonderful...”

Flora was the first to react with sparkling eyes, followed by Christina. The two had experienced the bath in the stone house on their return from Paladia to Galarc, so they were filled with more awe than surprise.

However, unlike the stone bath of the other house, this mansion’s bath was made of wood. The walls, floor, and bathtub were all made of wooden materials, creating a room that was overflowing with traditional Japanese taste.

“What a well-made bathtub...”

Liselotte’s eyes were first drawn to the bathtub. Most bathtubs in the Strahl region were of a shallow style that allowed just enough water to wash the body.

However, the new bathtubs Rio and the others had built were deep enough to soak in. On top of that, they were large enough to fit ten people with room to spare. It was filled to the brim with water and covered in a layer of steam. The wall, floor, and bathtub were entirely covered in wooden tiles that gave the bathroom a bright look. The window opened to a balcony that overlooked the back garden, allowing a half open-air bathing experience.

Unable to forget the feeling of a Japanese bath, Liselotte had also built a bathroom in her mansion back in Amande, but hers could only fit three people at most.

“Sir Haruto and Lady Alma remodeled the existing bathroom together. They recreated the bathrooms that could be found in Lady Satsuki and Lady Miharu’s previous world,” Charlotte explained, having enjoyed the bath yesterday.

“It’s truly wonderful...” Liselotte sighed dreamily. Maybe it was because she recalled her memories as a Japanese person, or perhaps she was plainly impressed by the brilliant bath before her.

Wait, hold on a minute... This mansion was given to him ten days ago, right? They built such a wonderful bath in just ten days? With only the two of them...?

Liselotte snapped back to her senses, tilted her head, and looked around at the bathroom once again, surprised by the degree of perfection. There was no sign of poor construction—everything was cleanly refined past the level of an amateur job. It certainly looked like the work of a carpentry company.

A top-notch swordsman with splendid cooking skills, and he makes his own fine wine as a hobby. He has knowledge of powerful sorcery and can also do carpentry work. Just how many talents do you have, Sir Haruto?

He had so much knowledge, Liselotte’s feelings surpassed mere awe and reached into the half-exasperated territory. But as a merchant, that made him all the more attractive to her. Each one of his areas of knowledge was packed with charm—if they were cleverly applied to business, they could lead to a huge fortune.

Thus, the correct thing to do as a profit-seeking merchant was to actively negotiate with him, and she was filled with the impulse to do exactly that, but...

For some reason, I find myself holding back. I don’t want to bring up business every time and make him think I only care about making money...

At present, she hadn’t been able to actively pursue such discussions. She might have failed as a merchant, but she couldn’t help feeling guilty about creating a self-interested relationship like that. Liselotte herself couldn’t really explain the reason why, so it was a source of concern for her.

“Is something the matter, Liselotte?”

Just then, Celia tilted her head at Liselotte, wondering why she had stopped at the entrance of the bathroom.

“Ah, no, it’s just such a lovely bathroom... I was wondering if it was difficult to make use of facilities like this. I’m sure water can be produced with magic, but preparing it each time must take some work, and then the water needs to be heated...”

“I shouldn’t be surprised you noticed that—how about I explain how this works?”

“Yes, please do.” Liselotte nodded.

“Then let’s do it while we wash up. Please, come this way. I’ll explain how to use the soap as well.”

With that, Celia led Liselotte over to the washing area. She explained how to use the shampoo, conditioner, and body wash.

“Umm... Celia? Where was this soap supplied from?” Liselotte asked after one sniff of the liquid soap that came out of the bottle. The Ricca Guild also stocked liquid body wash, but she was unfamiliar with the scent from this bottle.

She was also curious about the sorcery that cleansed and heated the water, but she left that topic aside for now. For the moment, her merchant side was far too interested in the soap right now.

“It’s all made by Haruto. He’s really knowledgeable about things like this.”

“Doesn’t he have too much knowledge?” In her shock, Liselotte accidentally spilled her inner thoughts from earlier.

“Hee hee, I know how you feel. Perhaps it’s because he’s lived a life without relying on others, but he tends to do everything by himself. I think that’s why he’s learned all kinds of things. He also seems fond of learning things he doesn’t know, and since he has a high level of expectation from himself...” Celia said with a strained smile.

Though that’s also what leads to his low self-esteem, she thought quietly.

“I see. He has the temperament of an artisan,” Liselotte said with a hum.

“Yeah, that’s probably true,” Celia nodded. That evaluation of him made sense.

“Are you talking about Sir Haruto?” Charlotte immediately joined the conversation. Naturally, Christina and Flora were right beside her, and they had all stopped in the middle of washing themselves to look on curiously.

“Yes. We were talking about how Haruto made this soap and how talented he is,” Celia summarized briefly.

“Indeed, Sir Haruto is a truly admirable person,” Charlotte agreed strongly.

“That’s not quite what I meant...”

“Ah ha ha...”

Celia and Liselotte both had strained smiles on their faces.

“That aside... This is my opinion one night after using Sir Haruto’s soap, but the quality is much better than the Ricca Guild’s soap,” Charlotte said cheerfully, looking at Liselotte.

“My interest has been piqued. Could you explain the difference for my research?” Liselotte asked, expressing her strong interest in the conversation as a merchant. Since Charlotte wasn’t the type of person to lie about things like this, she was extremely curious as to how it was better than her guild’s products.

“Scent is subjective, so there’s little that can be mentioned there. The biggest difference is in the cosmetic effect, I’d say. For example, for the shampoo, the difference is really evident in how smoothly I can comb my fingers through my hair the morning after. It may just suit my hair type in particular, but it feels so nice to touch even after I’ve slept. The body soap has also had a notable impact on my skin. It moisturizes for a much longer time than the Ricca Guild’s soap.”

“Those are all points we’ve been trying to correct in our products. We were still in the testing stage for an improved product, though...”

“Sir Haruto seems willing to explain how to create the soaps stocked here, so why don’t you use that knowledge for your store? If you’re satisfied with the result after trying it, of course.” Charlotte grinned boldly, as though she was confident in the answer. That wouldn’t be an issue, though—Liselotte trusted Charlotte’s opinion on items.

“That’s more than I could hope to ask for, but...is that really okay?”

“Yes, I’ve received Sir Haruto’s agreement last night, so I can mediate the deal. But there are some conditions: a portion of the sales must go to Sir Haruto, Lady Satsuki and I are to receive stock for our own use, and...Princess Christina and Princess Flora are to receive stock priority.”

Charlotte certainly worked fast—she hadn’t even forgotten to add a favor for Christina and Flora.

“Understood. Leave it to me.” Liselotte nodded smoothly.

“Thank you so much...” It was her first time hearing about the soap being prioritized for her, so Christina blinked in shock before giving her thanks. Her mouth was upturned in a happy smile.

She had enjoyed the soap in the stone house bath during her travels with Rio. It had changed her impression of baths, which she believed to be for cleaning purposes rather than enjoyment until then.

She had yearned to use that soap again after returning to Rodania and taking baths there, but she couldn’t say that to Rio out of modesty. To be able to have a safe supply of stock and enjoy this bath once again was most pleasing to her.

“Thank you very much!” Flora echoed in a cheery voice.

“Then it’s decided. Also, I’ve decided to try these soaking-style baths in the main castle. Sir Haruto and Lady Celia will be explaining the technology for that, but can I leave the remodeling to your guild as well?”

“Of course... But when you say ‘technology,’ do you mean this bathroom uses some kind of unique engineering after all?” Liselotte asked.

“There are magic artifacts to store water and keep it clean, which use unpublished spells that Haruto and I developed. We’ve decided to officially register the spell in Galarc and the Restoration in the near future, but...” Celia explained. Spell registration worked like patents on modern Earth. Whenever someone released a newly developed spell, they obtained the right to monopolize use of that spell. The kingdom closely managed published spells, ensuring that the developer received a fee every time it was used by someone else.

“They’ve agreed to teach the spells before doing so. Soaking-style baths can be combined with soaps as negotiation material, so I believe this could be the new trend,” Charlotte said, finishing Celia’s words. She didn’t clarify what kind of negotiation it was being used for but smiled with a meaningful look.

“I see...” Christina said.

“Noblewomen will swarm for it, I’m sure,” Liselotte guessed.

At present, the Ricca Guild handled the highest-quality soaps circulating in Galarc and Beltrum. The birth of a much better quality soap would certainly enthrall the customer base of royalty, nobility, and wealthy merchant women—especially if it had a remarkable effect on beauty. Once they experienced its effects, they would certainly want to continue using it. In which case, there were many ways to take advantage as the developer and supplier. It was the equivalent of obtaining a powerful weapon against the female half of the noble class.

While there haven’t been any movements yet, there are definitely people who dislike Sir Haruto’s rise in fame. It wouldn’t hurt to have as many options as possible.

Liselotte needed to prepare a counterattack in case something happened, increase her allies, and lay the foundations.

This was part of the reason why she requested Rio to give combat training and Celia to hold a lecture this time. Rio wasn’t affiliated with any particular faction, but he was clearly under the protection of King Francois and the Second Princess. Thus, the first people who needed to be on his side were the royal knights. This was why she had asked him to give the knights combat training—to give the participants a favorable impression of Rio. That plan had certainly turned out well.

On top of that, the fact that Celia—the famous genius sorcerer of Beltrum—was holding a lecture in Galarc especially out of her friendly relationship with Haruto Amakawa also gave the public a good impression of his connections.

Of course, that wouldn’t erase all of the animosity directed Haruto’s way.

But that works out anyway, since it just means things will get interesting. I can’t wait, Charlotte thought with a pleased smile.

◇　◇　◇

Once Rio’s combat training class ended, the participants were shown inside the mansion to mingle and have some lunch before they all returned to their posts.

However, the group was first led to the baths to wash up after all of the exercising they’d done. There were large baths in the mansion for men and women that were built by dividing the work between Alma and Rio, but the men’s bathroom was allocated to half of the group for them to wash up in. In the meantime, Rio used the small bathroom attached to his bedroom to clean himself.

Once that was done, he helped Miharu and the others with preparing lunch. The participants who had been washing up eventually returned to gather in the large dining room.

“Shall we begin soon, then?”

Charlotte took charge of the lunch party that commenced. There were multiple tables placed in the room, and there were no assigned seats to allow the attendees to interact with each other freely.

They could choose whether to stand and move around to talk as they ate, or to sit down and eat instead. The food was lined on the table in the center of the room for people to serve what they wished to eat onto their plates themselves.

“Lady Miharu and Lady Orphia prepared all of the dishes themselves. Sir Haruto prepared some as well, but please eat up before it gets cold—there’s no need to show any consideration for others. Enjoy yourselves without being too formal, yes? Now, let us begin.” Charlotte clapped her hands and wrapped up her short greeting. The knights seemed a little nervous to be in attendance among princesses.

“Let’s take Her Highness up on her offer.”

“It’s food made by Lady Miharu, Lady Orphia, and Sir Amakawa. It’d be rude to allow it to cool.”

The two captains of Galarc’s and the Restoration’s knights—Louise and Vanessa—led the way to the food. Their subordinates followed behind them.

“It feels a little strange being on the receiving side. And from those directly above me...”

Liselotte’s attendant, Natalie, looked a little uncomfortable as she spoke. Part of the reason was probably because she was the most serious out of the attendants, but she was also usually the one serving people, so she wasn’t used to this.

“You heard what the princess said: it’d be rude to refuse. Anyways, we’ve had Sir Haruto and Lady Miharu’s homemade cooking before and it was amazing, remember? It’d be a waste not to have some. Come on, let’s go.”

“Cosette, wait—”

Cosette started dragging Natalie over to the food table by the arm. Watching their backs was Aria, who called out to them with a sigh.

“Make sure not to go over the top, please. Goodness.”

Celia giggled and turned to Aria. “Hee hee, you’re a guest as well today. Forget about work and make sure you have lots to eat as well.”

“I’ve received more than enough of a welcome already. I was able to enjoy a splendid bath after the training, and now I’m attending this extravagant lunch. Honestly, it almost makes me wish I could work here,” Aria replied with a smile on her face.

Elsewhere in the room, Latifa was tugging Rio by the arm. “Onii-chan, we should get food too!”

“Sorry, I’m going to excuse myself and take a bath. I only washed myself briefly earlier.”

“Huh? Oh, should I come and help wash your back, then?” Latifa puffed up her cheeks when she heard Rio was leaving, but immediately smiled playfully to tease him.

“Of course not. I don’t want to concern people by being the only man in the room, so please enjoy yourselves without me for a while. The goal of this is for the attendees to interact with each other, after all.”

Rio gave a faint sigh of fond exasperation but patted Latifa’s head gently. Latifa squeezed her eyes shut at that, her expression softening in happiness.

“I’ll be back later.”

With those words, Rio quietly left the dining hall without drawing attention to himself. That being said, some people immediately noticed he was gone.

“Oh? Where is Sir Haruto going?” Charlotte, who had been talking to Christina and Liselotte, cocked her head and looked around at the others. This prompted everyone around her to look as well.

“He left to take a proper bath. He said we should enjoy things without him,” Latifa answered unhappily.

“Sir Haruto’s the owner of this mansion, so he shouldn’t have to show such reserve...” Charlotte looked somewhat sullen, pouting slightly.

“But it is a little awkward to be the only man in this room. This mansion’s like an all-girls high school right now—though it’s normally like this anyway,” Satsuki said sympathetically and looked around. There were dozens of people in the dining hall right now, including the waitstaff, and they were all women.

“Still, I didn’t expect him to disappear as soon as it began. I believe any gentleman of Sir Haruto’s age... No, any young and healthy gentleman would be delighted to remain in this room.”

The room was filled with beautiful women in the prime of their youth. Any noble in the prime of their manhood would have been proactively conversing with them.

“No, no. It’s because he’s a gentleman that he left to make us more comfortable.”

“That’s being too much of a gentleman.”

He’s probably what they’d call a “herbivore man” back home in Japan, Satsuki thought about Rio. Charlotte apparently found that displeasing and appeared to look sad.

“Hmm... I get what you’re trying to say, Char, but I think Rio’s lack of arrogance is a good thing.”

“I completely agree with that, but...I wish he would see his own charms in a more objective manner. Because everyone wants to talk to him.”

“Yeah,” Satsuki agreed.

After all, Haruto was the finest gentleman one could wish for. He was good-looking, had a good personality, was strong, high in status, and had a long list of achievements—it’d be hard to find any fault with him. On top of that, he was still sixteen years old and single. Even without the purpose of marriage, anyone would want to approach him. This was Satsuki’s line of thinking.

“I’m starting to understand everyone’s hardships. I expected more development in our relationship by spending time every day together, yet...” Charlotte sighed uneasily. She visited the mansion nearly every day to make various attempts at seduction, yet Rio was more passive towards romance than she thought. It wasn’t as though he was distancing himself from her, and he showed proper awareness of her as the opposite sex when she clung to him, but he never made a move on her.

“I’m glad you understand.” Latifa joined the conversation with a smug huff after hearing Charlotte’s lamentations. All her years spent with Rio hadn’t been for nothing—she understood those hardships too.

Watching that exchange a short distance away was Celia and her old friend Aria, as well as Natalie and Cosette.

“It seems like Sir Haruto left the room,” Natalie said, looking over at the conversation between Charlotte and the others she had just overheard.

“Aww, I wanted to use this chance to talk to him more... Whoa, this egg dish is amazing.”

“Don’t act disappointed and joyful in the same breath.”

Cosette’s shoulders slumped while she was tasting the food, making Natalie scold her with a fed-up look.

“Haruto will be back soon, I believe,” Celia said with a wry smile.

“Although it seems like there are many others who wish to speak to him, so there won’t be much time to talk to him...” Aria said, looking around the room.

The knights who were digging into the food had also noticed Rio’s absence, and some of them looked rather disappointed. They could be heard discussing how to approach him when he returned.

“If you want to talk to Haruto, do you want me to say something when he returns?” Celia offered thoughtfully.

“Really?” Cosette’s expression brightened as she leaned forward eagerly.

“S-Sure.”

Chapter 2: Preparing for Departure

Shortly before Rio began living in the Galarc Castle mansion...

At the farthest border of the Strahl region, a small nation was born. To any other kingdom, the existence of this nation would be seen as heresy.

It was called the Holy Democratic Republic of Erica. There was, of course, a reason why the Erica Nation (as it was called by its people) was seen as heresy: it was missing the one feature that every other nation in the Strahl region had in common, which was the presence of a king or emperor; an absolute ruler. There was no privileged class like nobility either.

This nation existed for the sake of its people. The nation didn’t function for its ruler or nobility, but for the sake of the citizens living there. People were born free and equal. That was the ideology behind the citizens who overthrew the royal rule.

Because of this, the citizens of this nation faced no social discrimination. There were no royals and nobles to discriminate against the citizens. The country moved by the hands of the people, for the sake of the people. In order to adhere to that way of life, the Holy Democratic Republic of Erica held an election to form a congress of representatives, creating a democracy where political decisions were made indirectly.

However, there needed to be something that could act as a symbol representing the nation. After its formation, Saint Erica was chosen by the first elected congress as the first head of state for leading the people in the founding moment of the nation. The nation itself was also named out of reverence for Saint Erica.

In the capital of Ericaburg, where the former royal capital once stood, the land was completely destroyed, as the liberators led by Saint Erica had invaded the capital to rally a revolution. The castle that protected the former king was now nothing but rubble, and the buildings in parts of the capital had been destroyed by the revolutionary army along the way.

However, despite this, the population living in the capital of Ericaburg was in high spirits. And it was all thanks to the absence of the royalty and nobility that had suppressed them with heavy taxes for so long.

Saint Erica had explained it was necessary to collect taxes for the nation, but she also declared that all the taxes would be used for the sake of the people. To back up that declaration, she took the fortune the royalty and nobility had hoarded and freely gave it out to the people in support of restoring the city.

Furthermore, because Erica was a beautiful woman in her mid-twenties, she was extremely popular amongst the people. The citizens worshipped her and worked diligently to restore the city.

Currently, Saint Erica herself was currently seated in the office of the building being used as the temporary official residence.

“Lady Erica, would you please reconsider things once more?”

Before her was a man pleading at her with a frown. His name was Andrei; he was a young man in his twenties, with a face that was serious and intelligent.

“No, Andrei. I’ve already decided.” Erica’s black hair fluttered as she shook her head slowly, a grin on her face.

“We will be extremely troubled if our head of state leaves so soon after the foundation of the country. You suddenly said you wanted to leave on a journey...” Andrei looked at Erica with an imploring gaze.

“This nation is my home, of course, and I still consider the people of this nation subjects of salvation. However, there are people in other countries being oppressed and stripped of their human rights. I have a duty to save those people just as much. There’s only one of me, so I’m afraid I have to act in order of precedence...” Erica said, sighing sadly.

“Lady Erica...” Andrei looked at Erica worriedly, but he also seemed greatly impressed, as his eyes were filled with reverence.

“Say, Andrei. The fact you’re worried is just proof of how much you’re relying on me, right? I’m very happy you think of me so highly.” Erica smiled at him gently.

“M-My Lady! I am undeserving of such words!” Andrei blushed faintly, shaking his head in a fluster.

“You’ve cooperated with me ever since I began my attempt to found this nation. I value you quite a bit. You’re an extremely dependable person. I’m able to leave on my journey because I know you’ll be here in this country. If it weren’t for you, I’d feel too uneasy about leaving.”

“Th-That’s... I am undeserving.”

“That’s not true. That’s why the congress and I appointed you as prime minister, in order to assist the head of state. In my absence, the prime minister will be the acting head.”

Andrei was originally the owner of a trading company, but was deeply impressed by Erica’s teachings of equality and provided support from the start of the revolution. Now that they had formed a new nation, he assumed the position of prime minister of the Holy Democratic Republic of Erica, the second in command to Erica.

“I cannot act as your replacement, Lady Erica...”

“Andrei, leading others is surprisingly easy,” Erica said gracefully to the doubtful man.

“That cannot be. Who could lead the people other than you? You, who thinks of the people above everything else...”

“I merely think of the people equally.”

“That’s exactly why. That’s what makes you a saint. You should be the one to guide the way. Everyone believed that when they chose you as leader.”

“While I do wish to respond to those feelings of yours, I...”

“...Your own feelings won’t change. I understand. Then please use the griffins to go on your trip. And take some people for protection.” Andrei hung his head in resignation.

“I’m sorry, Andrei.”

“Please don’t apologize.”

“I shall bring back a souvenir from my journey for you as an apology... That’s right, was it the Ricca Guild that you mentioned when we first met? A product of theirs might be nice. You said you wanted to stock some of their products in your shop, right?”

“You remember something like that...?”

“Of course.”

“Thank you very much... But I’ve already retired from being a merchant.” Andrei thanked her happily, but at the same time looked a bit saddened.

“But it was your dream, no? To make a deal with a world-famous merchant guild.”

“Well, yes...”

“Besides, deals aren’t limited to merchants. It’s possible for the country to make a trade deal as well.”

“Indeed, I can’t believe I missed such a thing.”

“And if the merchant guild is famous to that degree, it’d be most desirable to have them support our nation. I may try to meet their representative on my journey.”

“It’d be extremely reassuring to have them side with your teachings... But I’ve heard the president of the Ricca Guild is a noble daughter from a prominent Galarc family.”

“I don’t plan on making an enemy of every noble and kingdom. We are pacifists, after all. Let’s pray that the noble daughter representing the Ricca Guild agrees with our ideals,” Erica said to Andrei with the benevolent smile of a saint.

These were the events that happened several days before Erica left the country.

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, some time had passed since Rio started living in the Galarc Castle. Hiroaki often hung out with Rei and Kouta these days. Along with Roanna, the four of them gathered in Hiroaki’s room.

Recently, Hiroaki got into writing new stories. He took elements from fictional novels that thrived in Japan and tried to create a hit piece targeted to this world. Rei gave his thoughts from the view of a novel enthusiast, Roanna gave her advice as a noble of this world, and Kouta gave his opinion here and there. The plot Hiroaki wrote in Japanese was translated into the language of this world and entrusted to Roanna to be shared.

“This plot is the best, Hiroaki,” Rei said with excitement, having finished reading the newest story they had carefully refined.

“Right? I’m satisfied with this one.”

“Having two heroines was the correct choice. The face of this series is the unaging girl Cecillie, but Misally who opposes her is super cute as well. Any normal human would feel uneasy about aging, but the heroine’s charms are drawn out well. I can get behind this.”

“It’s the contrast between an unaging little girl and a regular little girl—that’s the main theme of this work. A regular little girl or an unaging girl, which is more attractive? That’s the question for the readers. If Misally’s charm as a heroine seems magnified by being the underdog, then that’s exactly what I planned,” Hiroaki said, self-satisfied, his nose held high with confidence.

“But if it isn’t written well, Cecillie will be swallowed up by Misally, yeah?”

“That’s where my skills come into play. I’m counting on your editing skills as well.”

“Leave it to me. I can’t wait to read the first draft. The plot is completed with this, right?”

Hiroaki waved a hand to calm Rei’s impatience. “Now, let’s not get ahead of ourselves. It wouldn’t be a problem to call this completed, but I have to get Kouta’s and Roanna’s opinions first. What do you two think?” In order to seek the thoughts of the two who had worked together with him until now, he looked at Kouta and Roanna with a pleased expression.

“I think it’s very interesting. However, I have a question rather than an opinion—do immortality elixirs exist in this world, Roanna?” Kouta asked.

“I don’t know if they exist, but research to create such elixirs has been conducted numerous times.”

“I see. So the people in this world are interested in such things too. By the way, is there a reason why the main character’s name is Koumei? I believe it’s the name of a famous tactician that appears in the Three Kingdoms, but...”

“Of course, it’s because I like Koumei,” Hiroaki answered immediately.

“I-I see...”

“What? You have a problem with that, Kouta?” Rei asked.

“No, it’s just that the name doesn’t exist in this world, so I was wondering what they would think of that... Since you’re translating the story into this world’s language, it’d be weird to write the name in Japanese.” Kouta raised a rather logical point.

“Yeah, I suppose a Japanese name would be odd, since it’d never be explained. But the main character’s name will be Koumei. I insist on using Koumei as the main character’s name in all my works. Anyway, the main character is a hero summoned from another world. It’d be weird for him to have a local name.”

“I see. That’s true... You have a point,” Kouta hummed, impressed.

“I know.” Hiroaki nodded smugly.

“Then the plot is complete like this. All that’s left is to write the manuscript, Hiroaki,” Rei said excitedly.

“Yeah. If I was being greedy, I would’ve liked to have a cute illustration of the heroines as character material. It’d help solidify my image of the heroines too. Having illustrations would also make it seem more like a light novel when it goes on sale, and it’d be an easy form of appeal to the readers.”

“Oh, don’t worry about that. Kouta can draw the illustrations,” Rei said.

“What?! Really?!” Hiroaki raised his voice in interest. Roanna’s eyes also widened.

“His mom was an art teacher. He’s been learning to draw since he was a kid, and he can draw whatever you want. He can draw cute girls too.”

“Hey now, if you had that kind of talent, you should have said so earlier.” Hiroaki grinned in delight.

“It isn’t that impressive,” Kouta replied weakly.

“Say, Kouta. You remember that cute illustration I asked you to draw for me before we came to this world? Draw that again.”

“All right, fine... It’s hard to draw with this pen and paper, so don’t expect it to be the same quality.” At Rei’s request, Kouta took the quill pen and paper in hand. With extremely practiced movements, he swiftly moved the pen across the paper.

Everyone watched Kouta’s work curiously.

“Wow, how are you so fast at drawing?” Hiroaki asked in wonder.

“It’s because I’ve made a copy of the original once before. There’s no need for me to think of the pose and composition again, and my hand remembers the lines. Though the tools make it harder to draw,” Kouta replied while moving his hand.

“Is that how it works...?” Hiroaki looked doubtful. Does this guy actually have a lot of artistic talent? he wondered to himself.

Several minutes later, Kouta’s hand stopped. “It’s a rough sketch, but it’s done.”

“Seriously? It’s Hiyori! And the quality is amazing, man.” Hiroaki’s eyes sparkled as he looked down at the completed illustration. It was an anime character that he knew well.

“As expected of a man of culture, Hiroaki.”

“I was a fan of her voice actor. She has such a nice voice.”

“Whoa, really? I completely agree. I have all her albums and concert Blu-rays, and I’ve joined her official fan club.”

“What? You should have said that earlier! I’m in the fan club too.”

“Well, we’ve only been talking about the plot lately.”

“That’s true...” Hiroaki looked down at the illustration again. “Hiyori’s so nice...” he murmured.

“She is indeed,” Rei echoed enthusiastically.

“What are the two of them talking about?” Roanna asked.

“I’m not sure myself, and I don’t think we need to know...” Kouta said.

“It’s decided. The illustrator for my work will be you, Kouta,” Hiroaki said, pointing at him.

“I don’t mind drawing the illustrations, but how long will it take to produce a novel?”

“It’ll have to be handwritten, so I won’t know until I’ve written it, but one volume’s worth of text should take at least one month to write.”

“What do you need for the illustrations?”

“The character designs for the main character and heroines, and some inserts for a selection of scenes would be nice.”

“In that case, the illustrations might take the same amount of time. Even if I worked alongside you, the fastest I could get a volume done would be one and a half to two months.”

“Yeah, that sounds fair. Come to think of it, what kind of plans did you guys have for the future?” Hiroaki asked, suddenly curious.

“Technically, we’re here on a temporary trip...”

“Who knows? I believe we’re returning when Princess Christina and Duke Huguenot leave the country, but...”

Kouta and Rei exchanged a look.

“I believe that is the correct assumption to have for now,” Roanna confirmed, having been in touch with Christina.

“I see... What kind of positions do you guys have in the Restoration, anyway?”

“I’m a baronet, and Kouta’s considered a guest. We’re attending the academy in Rodania out of Princess Christina’s kindness, learning about how to live in this world from now on.”

“Hmm, so you’re both students. But why did Rei get a baronet title while Kouta didn’t get one? Though it’s a bit late to be asking that...” Hiroaki looked at Kouta.

“Unlike Rei, I’m only staying in the Restoration temporarily.”

“Temporarily? You’re not joining?”

“I don’t intend to, no. Princess Christina did say I could do the same as Rei and receive a title if I joined, but...”

“Was there something else you wanted to do?”

“I actually wanted to try traveling as an adventurer,” Kouta answered shyly, scratching at his cheek.

“An adventurer? Whatever for?”

“I mean... I guess it’s because I want to grow up and become a real man...”

“Become a real man? Aha... I see. You’re a virgin, aren’t you? And you were made fun of for it, right?” Hiroaki sounded puzzled for a moment, but he immediately sensed something and pointed it out to Kouta.

“Wh-Why?! H-H-H-How did you...?!” Kouta’s voice cracked in a panic. Beside him, Roanna blushed awkwardly, while Rei burst out laughing.

“Heh. Boys of our age only say, ‘I want to grow up! Hmph!’ when their ideals have been twisted by being a virgin. You were rejected by the girl you liked, weren’t you?” Hiroaki guessed, grinning.

“Wow, bull’s-eye. As expected of Hiroaki.”

“I knew it.”

Rei and Hiroaki were highly amused.

“Wh-What’s wrong with that?!” Kouta snapped back, blushing.

“Ah, there’s nothing wrong with it. Wanting to go on a journey because you were rejected by a woman is good character development. I like those kinds of unpopular guys.”

“Guh... I-I’m sure it’s easy for you to say that when you have Roanna.”

“Y-You fool! H-High-ranked noblewomen like Roanna don’t engage in premarital relations!”

“Huh? R-Really?”

Kouta looked shocked. He looked between Hiroaki and Roanna nervously. “Th-Then that means...”

“...” Roanna flushed, but remained silent.

“B-Bastard, that’s sexual harassment! Don’t say such things in front of Roanna!”

Hiroaki showed a surprisingly innocent reaction. It seemed like he didn’t want Roanna to hear what they were talking about.

“W-Well, it’s your fault you started talking about virgins. Talking about virginity in front of a girl is sexual harassment in itself!” Kouta rebutted.

“It’s your fault for being a virgin!” Hiroaki declared.

“Indeed, Kouta’s a little sensitive about being a virgin,” Rei said, taking Hiroaki’s side.

“Ngh...” Kouta was unable to argue back after that.

“Tch... Hey, Kouta. Instead of journeying as an adventurer, get a girlfriend and graduate from being a virgin first,” Hiroaki advised, sighing tiredly.

“Wh-Why do I have to do that?”

“Because you’re a virgin.”

“S-Stop saying the word ‘virgin’ so many times... At least give me a reason.” Kouta frowned, sulking slightly.

“Let me say this bluntly: you’re still in love with that girl, aren’t you?”

“Wha...”

Having had his mark hit once again, Kouta blushed bright red. There was no need to confirm it with words.

“Your face is asking why I know, huh? The reason why you want to grow up is because you’re still attached to that girl who rejected you. You want to show her how you’ve grown,” Hiroaki continued, speaking the truth.

“Guh... Why do you sound so confident in your words? Hiroaki, you almost sound like...”

Like you’re a virgin as well—Kouta thought, looking at Hiroaki as he swallowed those words.

“Dumbass. Whatever. At any rate, you and Rei are my assistants now.” Hiroaki chuckled with a strangely calm smile.

“You just can’t decide that out of the blue...” Kouta said reluctantly.

“That’s fine, right, Rei?”

“Yeah, I don’t mind,” Rei agreed easily.

“Then it’s decided. The two of you are my assistants from today.”

“No, wait a minute.”

“What’s the problem? You’ll be working on the novel for the time being anyway. You can leave for your journey afterwards. Until you do, you can be my assistant. For now, be my exclusive illustrator,” Hiroaki decided rather forcefully. “Hey, Roanna. Prepare a position for these two. They’re becoming my assistants. At least raise Rei’s social rank,” he added before Kouta could protest.

“...I understand.” Roanna hesitated out of consideration for Kouta, but reluctantly nodded her head.

“Say, Rei. Are there any nice women this guy could be matched with?”

“Hmm... There’s this one girl called Mikaela Belmond. She’s on good terms with my fiancée and we often sit together during lectures.”

“Huh. Do you know her, Roanna?”

“I’ve never met her personally, but I believe she’s the daughter of Baron Belmond.”

“I see. A baron’s daughter, huh? Did those two come to this castle with you?” Hiroaki asked Rei.

“No, they’re both in Rodania.”

“Okay. Call her here with your fiancée.”

“Huh? Is it really that easy to call her here?”

Enchanted airships were a transport option, but they were normally used by high-ranked nobles and military alone. It wasn’t easy for a baron’s daughter to use them to travel. Moving an airship also required the permission of a noble or royal with a fairly high rank.

“It’ll just be a few hours by airship, right? By becoming my assistants, you’re becoming my subordinates. As your superior, I want to meet who you’re marrying. Please make those arrangements as well, Roanna.”

“As you wish.”

It was a different matter when the hero was giving the orders. Roanna didn’t show any particular objections either as she nodded.

“Thanks,” Hiroaki said in satisfaction. “Now. Let’s hear more about how you were rejected, eh?”

The conversation moved on to the story of how Kouta had his heart broken.

◇　◇　◇

One night, half a month after Rio began teaching his combat classes, Rio, Miharu, Celia, Latifa, Aishia, Sara, Orphia, Alma, and a visiting Satsuki gathered in the dining hall of the mansion. They had all finished eating and were enjoying post-dinner tea.

Rio looked around at everyone and started speaking somewhat formally. “I have something serious I’d like to discuss today, if that’s all right. It mostly concerns Satsuki, Sara’s group, and Celia and Miharu.”

Everyone exchanged puzzled glances with each other.

“Sure... What is it?” Satsuki asked on behalf of the group.

“I wanted to have a proper discussion about the future.”

“The future...?”

“What I want to do might not be aligned with what you all want to do, so I want to hear everyone’s thoughts. There’s also some information I wanted to pass on,” Rio explained, casually glancing over at Sara and Latifa.

“I see. How considerate—though typical of you, I suppose.” Satsuki chuckled, finding the way Rio didn’t decide things for everyone without asking first to be a positive aspect of his personality.

“First, I believe I’ve mentioned this before, but I’m thinking of leaving in another three or four weeks. It’ll be another two months or so before I return again,” Rio said, revealing the first order of business.

“Can I ask where you’ll be going...?” Satsuki asked slowly, watching Rio’s expression.

“Of course. The first stop will be the village where Sara and the others are from. After that, I’ll be heading to my parents’ hometown.”

“Their hometown? That’s in...”

“The Yagumo region.”

“Right. Isn’t that really far? It’s past the vast wasteland east of the Strahl region. I heard it’s really dangerous...” Satsuki looked at Rio as though to question how he’d get there.

“Traveling by foot would take years, but it can be reached in less than a month through the air. However, even then, it’s a dangerous trip...”

With no map or compass, there was no choice but to travel while relying on the position of the sun, limiting movement to the daylight hours. There were dangerous creatures in the sky and on the ground, and abnormal weather sometimes prevented one from flying altogether.

“Huh... So if you went by air, it’d take two months just to get there and back.”

“Well, yes,” Rio said. Using a teleportation crystal to the spirit folk village would shorten the return trip, but explaining that now would derail the conversation.

“But what are you going to the Yagumo region for when it’s such a long trip?”

“I want to give my relatives an update on what’s been going on.”

“Huh? You have family in the Yagumo region?” Satsuki’s eyes were wide. She thought Rio had been born and raised in the Strahl region, where he’d lost his parents at a young age and become an orphan. It didn’t feel right to ask about his past, so she hadn’t known he had actually been to Yagumo before.

“I haven’t mentioned it to you before, but yes.”

“Wow, so you’ve met them before?”

“Yes.”

“Huh. I kind of want to meet them. What are they like?” Satsuki asked. Miharu and Celia also fixed their stares on Rio.

“They’re my paternal grandmother and cousin. And my maternal grandparents too.”

“I see, I see. Is your cousin a boy? Or a girl?”

“She’s a girl who’s one year older than me...”

“Which makes her the same age as me, huh? Aww, now I really want to meet them!”

“The main issue is this: Sara’s group will return to their village to give their updates to their families as well, but what will the rest of you do? If you come along, you won’t be returning to the Strahl region for two months. Visiting my relatives is purely my own personal matter, so you can stay in this mansion if you wish...”

There was also the option to wait at the spirit folk village instead.

“Yes! I want to go with you! Your family is my family too. I need to greet them properly,” Latifa immediately replied, raising her hand.

“I’m also staying with Haruto,” Aishia added.

“It’ll depend on whether the elders give permission, but we’re also thinking of going with you to Yagumo after visiting the village.” Sara sent Orphia and Alma a signal with her eyes before quietly expressing their intentions.

“Yes! I want to go too!” Satsuki also raised her hand energetically.

“You can’t leave the castle, Satsuki.”

There was no way she could casually leave the castle to go all the way to Yagumo.

“Yeah, but...” Satsuki puffed up her cheeks in a cute protest.

“What about Miharu and Celia?”

“Umm, I...” Miharu looked at Satsuki hesitantly. Perhaps she felt guilty Satsuki was being left behind all alone.

“It’s fine, Miharu. You can leave me. I’m just sulking because I know I can’t go,” Satsuki persuaded Miharu with a wry smile.

“Yes. But there’s also the matter of Aki and the others...”

“Oh, right. It’s true some time has passed since we all split up, so it makes sense that you’d be wondering what they’re up to. And now you’ll be gone for at least two months.”

They had decided to wait patiently for time to pass, but several months had gone by since they split. It made sense to feel curious about how they were doing.

In fact, Miharu hung her head with a hesitant expression.

After weighing all her options in her heart, she finally decided on prioritizing her own feelings and raised her head. She then turned to Satsuki near pleadingly.

“Is it... Is it okay if I go along too?”

“Of course. Leave things to me in your absence.” Satsuki was pleased Miharu had prioritized herself for once—and perhaps a little pleased to be relied on—as she thumped herself in the chest and accepted the request.

“I’ll send a letter to Masato and ask if there’s been any progress. There should be a reply by the time you return, so look forward to it.”

“Thank you so much, Satsuki.”

Satsuki shook her head shyly at the way Miharu bowed deeply at her. “It’s fine—nothing to thank me for. What are friends for?”

“I’m counting on you too, Satsuki.” When Rio bowed at her, Satsuki made an even more embarrassed face.

“Sure thing.”

“That leaves Celia. What will you do? There’s the Restoration to consider, as well as the main Beltrum Kingdom’s problems. You can stay in this mansion if you wish, but...”

She must be worried about how her family is doing back home, Rio thought as he looked at Celia.

Celia paused for a brief moment, but answered with a bright smile. “No... I’m your assistant right now. I’m going too, of course.”

“Are you sure?”

“Yes. I’ve received some information about the main government, and my family doesn’t seem to be in any immediate danger. There’s nothing in my power I can do to help the Restoration’s relationship with Beltrum. Only Princess Christina can be entrusted with that. Besides, she left you to me...” Celia trailed off, staring at Rio.

Rio tilted his head, puzzled. “...Is there something else?”

“Yeah. Well, I want to meet your relatives too...” Celia said a little shyly.

“I understand. Then I’ll take you to the Yagumo region as well.”

“Okay.” Celia nodded happily.

“The first one to meet them will be me, your little sister!” Latifa puffed up her cheeks.

“I know,” Rio agreed with a strained smile.

“That means it’d be better for us to return to the village first. I’d love to show Celia the village, and the elders need to give their permission for that,” Sara suddenly suggested, exchanging looks with Orphia and Alma.

“You mean the three of you will go back first?” Rio asked after a pause.

“Yes. I don’t believe there’ll be a problem if she shows up at your referral, but it’s probably better to give advance warning.”

“So you’ll be returning here after you’ve received confirmation...?”

“Yes, exactly.”

In other words, the three of them would be traveling through the Wilderness alone. It wasn’t likely that anything bad would occur, but there were creatures there that even Sara and the others would struggle against.

“I can go,” Rio offered.

“You’re the owner of this mansion, so you should stay here. And please trust in our abilities a little more. It’s nice that you care about us, and I know we’re no match for you or Aishia, but we’re still strong enough to face the Wilderness,” Sara said, looking at Rio with scornful eyes.

“...”

“You guys...” Celia began to speak but was interrupted.

“Oh, don’t apologize or thank us, please.”

“Yes, we’re not doing this just for Rio’s or Celia’s sake.”

“It’s simply something we wanted to do.”

Orphia, Alma, and Sara all made comments in anticipation of what Rio and Celia were about to say.

“I understand... In that case, please use the teleport crystal in my possession on your way there. That should reduce the duration and risk of your trip by half,” Rio said.

Sara nodded with satisfaction. “All right. We’ll take you up on that offer.”

“Teleport crystal... That’s the name of the artifact that was used when Princess Christina and Princess Flora were abducted, right?” Satsuki asked, blinking.

“Yes. I possess one as well.” Rio gave the explanation on teleport crystals he’d omitted earlier. Satsuki could be trusted, so there was no need to keep it a secret.

“Huh? Wow! So you can warp if you have that?” Satsuki asked in great interest.

“Yes, but not freely. The destination is limited to Sara’s village, and the trip can only be made one way.”

“That’s still amazing, though.”

“Indeed. That’s why I’d appreciate it if you kept this a secret from anyone else. This is a particularly valuable item made from sorcery that’s considered lost in the Strahl region. If it’s stolen, Sara’s village will also be at risk of invasion.”

“Right, got it.” Satsuki nodded with a serious look.

Rio continued with a glance at the spirit folk girls. “Also, I wanted to use this opportunity to talk about Sara and the others.”

“Are you sure? They’re from a secret village, so you can’t speak too much about it, right? And with artifacts like this, I can imagine why...” Satsuki also looked over to check their expressions. The only thing she knew was that they lived in a hidden village at the outskirts of Strahl.

“This is at the request of the people involved.”

Sara and the others had gone to Rio, asking him to explain things properly to Satsuki before they departed. They also considered telling Charlotte, but ultimately decided not to this time because of her position as royalty. That being said, their trust in Charlotte was indeed high enough for her to be considered at all.

“We want to get closer to Satsuki, so we discussed things amongst ourselves and decided not to keep secrets. We knew you were always acting considerate towards us,” Sara said.

“It felt like there was a distance between us—like we were making a wall. And we didn’t want that,” added Orphia.

“That’s why we’d appreciate it if you hear us out,” Alma disclosed.

“Thank you...” Satsuki said shyly. “But it’s a rule of your village, isn’t it? You don’t have to break it for me.”

“Yes. But there are exceptions to the rules,” Sara answered a little bashfully. Thus, Satsuki found out the truth behind the spirit folk girls and their village. The girls departed for the village two days later.

Chapter 3: Reunion at the Village

Roughly three weeks later, Sara and the others returned to Strahl from the spirit folk village. Sara’s contract spirit, Hel, snuck into the mansion in spirit form and informed everyone of their return. Rio slipped out of the mansion that night to make his way to the stone house where Sara and the others were staying at the outskirts of the capital.

“Sorry for dropping by so late,” Rio said.

“Not at all. Please, come in,” said Sara, and Rio entered.

Invited by Sara, Rio went through the front door.

“Long time no see, Rio.”

“Good evening.”

Orphia and Alma were also there to greet him.

“I’m glad to see the three of you are well. Has anything new happened?”

“Yes. We’ve gotten permission to bring Celia to the village. The teleport crystal has been recharged with magic essence, so it’s ready to go whenever.”

“I understand. We’ll probably leave within the next few days, then.”

“Okay. But there was something else... I’m not sure whether it can be classified as a problem, but there are people who want to meet you once we return to the village,” Sara said to Rio in a rather hesitant tone.

“Meet me? I don’t mind... But may I ask who it is?” Rio cocked his head in question.

“About that... We were asked not to say anything so that the explanation can be given directly. Could you wait until we return to the village to hear the details?” Sara scratched her cheek, unsure of how to explain things.

“All right. That’s fine too.” He couldn’t really understand the situation, but if Sara was the one saying this, then there must be a reason. Rio wasn’t the type of person to pry. He nodded easily and decided to wait until they reached the village.

◇　◇　◇

Several days later, it was time for Rio and the others to depart for the spirit folk village. Standing at the front door of Rio’s estate were Satsuki and Charlotte, who had come to see them off. Francois had given his farewells in advance, while Rio and Celia had visited Christina and Flora to inform them of their absence. Liselotte had also said her goodbyes, so none of them were present to see them off right now.

“I can’t believe you’ll be gone for another two months... I’ll be lonely.” Charlotte puffed up her cheeks in a sulking manner, looking up at Rio from a close distance. Any growing boy unaccustomed to girls would’ve been blown away on the spot.

“I plan on staying in the mansion for a while next time I return.” Rio averted his eyes awkwardly. Latifa’s eyes glinted beside him.

“Princess Charlotte, that’s a little too close.”

“We’re about to be separated, so I’m being close on purpose.” Charlotte moved forward even more, closing the gap between her and Rio until there was nothing left. She leaned her upper body against Rio’s chest.

“Onii-chan!” Latifa’s voice was nearly a scream. The only reason why she didn’t tear Charlotte away at a moment’s notice was because she was aware the other person involved was, indeed, a princess. Miharu and Celia were similarly aware of this, but their personalities prevented them from doing anything but watch on nervously.

“Princess Charlotte, your jesting has gone a little too far.” Rio placed his hands on Charlotte’s shoulders and slowly tried to place distance between them. However—

“I’m not joking, though...”

Charlotte immediately took Rio’s right hand in a graceful movement and quietly brought it to her cheek. She then proceeded to touch his fingers with her lips.

“Oops, I’ve kissed you.” There was a faint blush on her cheeks. She added some comments about how it was her first time and how she wouldn’t do such a thing as a joke.

Chapter 5: The Saint’s Development

Some time passed, and soon it became time for Rio and the others to depart from the Karasuki Kingdom for the Strahl region once more.

Far away in the Strahl region, five people were walking through the Galarc Kingdom’s trade capital of Amande, home to the headquarters of the Ricca Guild. They were all dressed in travel clothes; one of them was Saint Erica, who had visited the Proxia Castle by herself just the other day.

“This is Amande. A rather bustling city, it seems.”

Erica looked around at the cityscape, impressed by what she saw. The expressions of the people she passed were all energetic and lively, and the many patrolling soldiers meant the public order in the city was good too. Either the streets were well maintained or the residents were highly conscious of appearances, as there was no rubbish on the streets or strange smells coming from the alleyways, making the city appear quite beautiful.

“The faces of the people are bright, though not as much as those of our nation. The rumored noble lady governing this city must be quite good at her job, Lady Erica,” the female swordsman accompanying Erica said to her. The others around them also gave their approval for Amande in pleasant surprise.

However, none of them were willing to back down from their stance of their newly established motherland being better. Part of the reason was because of their pride, but the biggest reason was because they worshipped Erica as their saint. As people who were guided by Saint Erica, their lives were naturally better—this was something they believed without any doubt.

The four accompanying Erica were voluntary followers, here to protect her as an elite guard. Among them were those who were born as nobility, people who had served the original kingdom that Erica destroyed, religiously converted after being guided by Erica’s numerous miracles and teachings.

“I don’t doubt that our people are living better either. However, this isn’t just the work of good governing. We’ve traveled through many cities, but has there ever been one this developed? We should refer to this city for the development of our own nation, don’t you think?” Erica said, correcting the mistake her followers had made.

“Indeed...”

“If we could reproduce this splendid city in our own nation...”

“We should speak to the person who developed this city.”

The followers didn’t deny it. They always believed the words of the saint were true, and everything they said was always based on this premise.

Erica ignored them.

The standard of this city is far above the average of a Strahl city. There’s no way it could have developed this much without someone’s guidance. The only thing I thought was worth using was the Ricca Guild and the title of its head, but... Liselotte Cretia, huh? My interest has been piqued.

She found herself having a personal interest in Liselotte, the governor of Amande and president of the Ricca Guild. Her mouth twisted.

“Hey, you pretty adventurer ladies...and the pretty black-haired lady over there!”

A stall owner called out to Erica’s party. Their travel clothes seemed to have made him assume they were adventurers.

“...Me?” Erica pointed to herself. Black-haired people were extremely rare in the Strahl region. Her attention caught by the word “black-haired,” Erica looked around the area for anyone else fitting that criteria, but there was only herself. Figuring the man was just selling his stall product, Erica looked away again in disinterest.

“How about some of Amande’s famous soup pasta?”

“Pasta, you say...? The product you’re selling is... Hmm.” Erica seemed to think something after hearing the stall owner pronounce “pasta” and looked over at the ingredients behind the counter. Her eyes widened when she spotted the rod-shaped dried noodles and she immediately paused to think.

“I sell soup pasta here. Ha ha, I bet this is your first time seeing pasta!”

“That’s not the case, but... Pasta, hmm. If you don’t mind, could you show me the way you say that more clearly?”

Erica’s attention was still focused on the sound of the word “pasta.” She fixed her gaze on the man’s lips to confirm the word he was saying.

“S-Sure? P-Pasta?” Under her observant gaze, the stall owner repeated the product name in confusion.

“And just to confirm, this is how you say pasta...?”

Erica kept the dried noodles in the stall within her view while staring at the man’s mouth and confirming the fact once again.

“Y-Yeah. What’s the big deal? You’re pretty, but you’re a weird one, miss.” The man’s confusion only increased with the repeated questions and Erica’s fixed gaze on his mouth.

“Pardon my rudeness... I was just a little curious. May I have one order of soup pasta? It’s just about lunchtime, so we may as well eat here. Please make a serving for all of us.” Erica smiled warmly to ease the man’s caution.

“S-Sure. Coming right up!” The man nodded, slightly startled.

“May I watch you make it as well?”

“Yeah, go ahead.”

“Thank you very much.” Erica walked past the stall counter and stared at all the cooking utensils from beside the stall owner. She then fixed her gaze on the dried noodles once more.

“By the way, you called this Amande’s ‘famous pasta’ earlier. Who was the one who invented this?” she asked the owner.

“Hmm? Oh, this ingredient was invented by the Amande governor and Ricca Guild president, Lady Liselotte Cretia. It started selling in Amande several years ago, and now it’s a staple food as common as bread in this city. The neighboring kingdoms have started to use this ingredient more as well,” the stall owner answered proudly.

“I see. Only a few years ago, huh...”

“What’s wrong? You seem oddly pleased.” The stall owner’s eyes widened slightly, peering at Erica’s face.

“Nothing. I’m just glad I made the trip to this city. Thanks to that, I’m about to be blessed by a very good meeting,” Erica said, the corners of her mouth rising in a grin.

◇　◇　◇

Roughly one hour later, inside an office at the Amande governor building...

“Say, Aria... Isn’t there a strangely large amount of paperwork today?” Liselotte had just finished her lunch and sat down in her office to do work, when her expression twitched at the mountain of paperwork on her desk.

“They’re documents for the beginning of the mass production of the soap products Sir Amakawa designed. We’re halting the production of the Guild’s current soap products and expanding operations, so the documents mounted up,” Aria answered smoothly, having skimmed the paperwork in advance. They were discarding the old production line and starting over from scratch, so everything from the continued employment of the old workers to the cost calculations of the new hires had to be checked.

“Ah, I see. I don’t know whether to be happy or sad...” Liselotte chuckled with a strained smile. Because she was hesitant before the stack of papers, she was having trouble getting started.

“Give up and begin your work already.”

“I-I know...” At Aria’s sigh, Liselotte pouted cutely. She normally acted maturely, so it wasn’t a gesture she would show before others, but when she was in front of Aria she showed girlish expressions appropriate for her age.

“Let’s clean this up.” With that said, Liselotte finally reached for the mountain of papers. It was at that moment when someone knocked on the door.

“Come in.” Liselotte looked at the door and gave her permission for whomever it was to enter. It was the newest attendant-in-training, Chloe.

“A visitor has arrived without an appointment, saying she wants to visit the head of the Ricca Guild. She’s at the gate of the noble district right now, and...I’ve never heard of her before, but she says she’s Saint Erica.”

There were quite a few great figures throughout history referred to as saints, but when it came to those alive in the modern day, that number reduced significantly. If an unknown person was a self-proclaimed saint, it was almost guaranteed to be a lie.

Chloe had been ordered by Liselotte to always report any visitors who arrived, but the words, “There’s a suspicious lady out here calling herself a saint. What will you do?” were written on her face in invisible ink. Meanwhile...

“Saint Erica... Isn’t that...”

“It’s the name of the person who incited the people of a small vassal nation of the Proxia Empire into revolution not too long ago, I believe.”

Liselotte and Aria recognized the name.

“Could it be the same person? If so, does she want the Galarc Kingdom on her side after making an enemy of the Proxia Empire? But then why would she come to Amande instead of the capital...?” Liselotte cocked her head, considering the possibilities.

“It could be someone else who’s mistaken the Ricca Guild for a charity,” Aria said. In fact, that was the more likely possibility.

“Hmm, but doesn’t it make you a little curious?” Liselotte said, placing the paper in her hand back on top of the pile on her desk.

“Even if you escape reality, the work isn’t going anywhere...”

“Th-This is work too. Yes, work. Information gathering! Information is the lifeline of both merchants and nobles! Better to see this for myself than listen to hearsay!” Liselotte said, as though to convince herself, then stood up.

“Treat her the same as any first-time visitor and show her to the estate, Chloe,” she directed.

“Understood.” Chloe bowed once and left the room.

“As usual, you’ll be present with me. Treat it as an extended lunch.”

“As you wish.” Aria nodded in resignation with a smile on her face.

◇　◇　◇

And so, roughly half an hour later...

With Aria as her guard, Liselotte stepped inside the meeting room of the Amande governor’s building. Seated on the sofa inside the room was Erica.

When Liselotte entered the room and first spotted her, she froze for a moment to swallow her breath.

She’s Japanese, right...? No matter how you look at it...

Erica’s facial features were clearly that of a Japanese person. She wore a dress that would definitely be dismissed as cosplay in Japan. It was a normal design for those in holy positions in this world, but it had quite an impact on Liselotte, who had memories of her life in Japan... Especially since it was coming from a self-proclaimed saint.

So this is the saint who destroyed a kingdom... The sixth hero? There’s been no information on her until now... It was the right decision to meet her.

Since she was going out of her way to make contact, there must have been something she wanted to discuss with Liselotte. Perhaps she’d be able to get some useful information out of her as well. It was because these things could happen that she didn’t ignore visitors with no appointments. That was Liselotte’s way of doing things.

“Is something the matter? You took a look at my face and seemed surprised... You are Liselotte, right?”

Erica stood up quietly when Liselotte entered and bowed in a polite manner. She gazed at Liselotte’s face with a giggle and asked what was wrong.

“No, it’s nothing... You must be Saint Erica. As you said, I am the president of the Ricca Guild, Liselotte Cretia. I’m also the governor of this city.”

“Nice to meet you. I’m Erica. I was worried my title of saint would sound too shady for you to meet me, so I’m pleased to be able to meet you,” Erica said, joking about how she thought her own title was suspicious as well.

“I’ve actually heard your name before, so I wanted to meet you myself. Please have a seat,” Liselotte said, sitting herself down across from Erica.

“Why, really? You’ve heard of me?” Erica had a fake smile of delight on her face as she sat down.

“I heard a rumor on the wind not long ago. A revolt occurred in a small kingdom, giving birth to a new developing nation. The person who led the people at the time was called Saint Erica, I believe.”

That’s you, isn’t it? Liselotte stared at Erica as though to imply that.

“Oh my, is that so? I’m surprised information travels so fast in a world like this. Yes, I am Erica.”

“I see...”

She confessed to the truth so easily, Liselotte was thrown off balance for a moment. The kingdom that fell was an unimportant minor nation located at the remote frontier, so it hadn’t attracted much attention. But she hadn’t expected Erica to acknowledge that she led a nation into ruin so easily. Admitting to it could result in her being considered a security risk.

“Were you on your guard because you thought I was the one who led a kingdom to destruction?” Erica asked jokingly, having seen through Liselotte.

Liselotte answered after a brief pause. “If I judged things by only focusing on the negatives of the results, that would be the case. However, there are reasons behind everything that happens. I won’t be able to give a proper evaluation without considering both the process and the results.”

“Oh my, what a wonderful view you have.” Erica giggled elegantly.

“Not at all... So why did you want to meet me today?”

“You have an interest in me, I see. That makes me very happy. And the same goes for me as well. I gained an interest in the Ricca Guild that gained so much fame in our nation, and in you personally. I came here because I wanted to meet you.”

“So you came to see me out of curiosity?” Liselotte asked indirectly if she was just here to meet her, and not for any other goal.

“Meeting you isn’t my only goal, of course. I wanted to scout you.”

“Scout me?” Liselotte looked confused at the unexpected answer.

“Yes. I would love for you to move to our nation and lend your strength in developing it. Just like how you did for Amande here,” Erica said, starting a completely erratic topic.

Liselotte was the daughter of Count Cretia, the leading noble of the Galarc Kingdom, and she was also the president of the Ricca Guild. Asking her to move to a remote unknown nation would normally be unthinkable. In fact, it was so preposterous, her invitation sounded like a joke... But Erica didn’t seem to be joking.

“I am a noble of the Galarc Kingdom. I cannot do such a thing,” Liselotte said with a serious look.

“Oh dear. What do I have to do for you to accept, then?” Erica didn’t seem to be aware of how ridiculous her request was; her questions were worded under the assumption Liselotte could be convinced.

It’s hard to tell how serious she is... At a glance, she has a well-mannered smile, but...

It felt like she was talking to someone wearing a mask. Being invited to something so tremendous immediately after meeting left Liselotte feeling wary towards Erica.

“It would be one thing to temporarily visit kingdoms we have friendly relations with, but did you think a noble would be able to accept an invitation from an unknown nation so easily? Asking me to migrate is equal to asking me to abandon my country. At worst, it would be seen as inciting a fight with my motherland,” Liselotte said, emphasizing her strong disapproval of the situation. Erica’s invitation was asking her to betray her homeland.

It was at this moment that Erica finally frowned. “So the obstacle is your country, you’re saying. You’re a noble of the Galarc Kingdom, so you can’t move to another.”

“Even if I weren’t a noble, I cannot think of a reason to move to your nation. I love this country, and I’m proud of this city that I govern.”

“I see. However, royalty and nobility govern over the people as the privileged class. Don’t you think this could create a chain of misfortune?”

“What are you suddenly talking about now...?” Erica’s question was a little too risky to take as dark humor, so Liselotte questioned her with a searching expression.

“I’m saying royalty and nobility only stand in the way of the development of the world.”

“I am part of the royalty and noble class too...”

Liselotte frowned at being told such things to her face. She was on the verge of feeling fed up with this conversation.

“However, when you move to our nation, you’ll discard your rank as nobility. Since we have no royalty or nobility in our country,” Erica said, as though the conclusion was set already. Liselotte had lots of experience talking to people who had their own conclusion decided with no intention of listening, but Erica surpassed them all by far.

“And I’m saying I have no intention of migrating...”

The conversation wasn’t meshing well, causing Liselotte to add more emotion behind her tone as she denied Erica.

A clattering sound went off in the room; the source was immediately behind Liselotte, coming from Aria. She had dropped her writing pen.

“Excuse me.” Aria bowed with just those words, but she wasn’t the head attendant for nothing. She had made an unexpected sound on purpose, getting her master to reset her thoughts. Sensing that, Liselotte let out a small sigh and thanked Aria in her heart.

Thanks, Aria.

“You were saying royalty and nobility only harm the development of the world, right?”

She tried to correct the trajectory of the topic. The conversation was scattered all over the place, so she focused on one aspect of it.

“The privileged class bled the people of my small nation dry for many, many years. Do you know the reason why?” Erica asked again.

“They weren’t blessed with good rulers, I suppose...”

She wasn’t wrong. But Liselotte frowned anyway, believing there was no perfect answer.

Meanwhile...

“You seem to have an understanding. If I were to reword it more thoroughly, it would be because a status-based monarchy is an extremely imperfect social system.”

Erica smiled in satisfaction, delving deeper into Liselotte’s answer with her words.

“You must face it—the fact that accepting the framework of a privileged class creates a system where they get to line their pockets more. As long as the ruling class is given free rein, the citizens must entrust the stability of their lives to the good will of the rulers. As a result, a world where the people are continuously exploited is created. This is a common problem in many of the kingdoms of this world. Wouldn’t you agree?”

She raised a question to Liselotte that tested her loyalty as nobility. If Liselotte replied that it wasn’t a problem, her words would be perceived as the royalty and nobility class being unwilling to lose their privilege and have equality with the common class.

If she had asked Nidoll Proxia the same question, he might have responded that he didn’t have a problem with it.

“Even if that were true, it’s not something I can fix,” Liselotte said.

“Isn’t that because you refuse to throw away your privilege as a noble? You wish to use the people as a stepping-stone for sweet benefits. Am I wrong?”

“I won’t deny that I was raised in a blessed environment. But that doesn’t mean I will step on the citizens to exploit them. I govern Amande with the people in mind, aiming to create equality as much as possible.”

“Indeed, Amande is a lovely city. The people are brimming with life. But that is only because you’re governing this city. What if someone else took over the rule of this city in the future, causing the life of the people to deteriorate? Don’t you think we should create a system to prevent such a thing?” Erica asked question after question, all of which were made to sound just. Any royalty or nobility with virtuous values would have trouble answering them.

“Even if I did, that would be difficult. Like I said, it’s not something I can fix.” Liselotte answered with a look of pained endurance.

Erica tilted her head curiously. “Why do you think it’s difficult? It’s easy. We just have to give the decision-making right of the city to the people in a council form. Are you saying you can’t do that?”

“It isn’t that simple at all. If you wanted to do that, you’d need to develop the education of the people first. When the people involved in political decision-making are unreliable, the group will self-destruct. Alternatively, those in the know will take advantage of that foolishness to bend politics to their own convenience. That will just give birth to a new privileged class. There are issues in forcing democracy onto the people from above, so even if education develops, such obstacles will never be completely removed.” Liselotte listed the issues with the matter Erica called simple, giving a logical rebuttal.

“You really are intelligent. You understand that people are actually beasts at heart. And the fact that will never change no matter how much society advances. You understand it perfectly. How wonderful. Yes, that’s why I...” Erica’s eyes widened faintly. Something seemed to stab her in the heart, as the smiling mask she had on until now slipped, showing a painful expression underneath. She grit her teeth as though she were holding back a strong grudge towards something. That was the first humanlike expression Liselotte saw from her.

“What are you saying...?” Liselotte looked at Erica questioningly.

“Pardon me. The thought of someone as intelligent as you not being in our nation got me all heated up.” Erica pasted her smiling mask on her face once again. The mask of a saint...

“I think I understand how you led your people and created a nation based on our conversation just now,” Liselotte summarized with a sigh.

“Oh? Isn’t that impressive. Would you be willing to share that with me?” Erica asked with widened eyes.

“It’s because you think of the people, isn’t it?” Liselotte replied.

“Heh. Heh heh heh. Ha ha ha.” Erica laughed loudly.

“What’s so funny?”

“Oh, nothing. I merely wish to create a world where the weak don’t exist. As a start, I created a democratic nation for the people, by the people... To put it in another way, it’s my grand plan for revenge.”

“Revenge, you say...”

“Yes. That’s why creating a world where the weak don’t exist is simply a means. My goal is revenge.”

“I’m not sure I follow what you’re saying...” Just as she thought they could have an intelligent conversation, this happened. Liselotte had a tired look on her face.

“Our chat has been extremely meaningful. That’s why I’d like to invite you one more time. Liselotte Cretia, please throw away your status and come to my nation...to create a country where everyone is equal.”

“I refuse... I’m sure a country where everyone is equal would be wonderful. But creating such a place is impossible. You criticize the rule of royalty and nobility, saying the people should be the ones to govern the country, but there are a mountain of issues that have to be addressed for that to work. I believe the current system is better in comparison. If things need to change, then that change will happen slowly. In my opinion, inciting the people into a sudden revolution is not the right move.”

That would only lead to destruction. Liselotte gave her opinion on the subject fluently.

“You’re rejecting me no matter what?”

“Yes. In fact, I don’t get it. Why are you so fixated on me as an individual...?” Liselotte said, showing a glimpse of her confusion.

“To be honest, I originally had my eye on the Ricca Guild’s influence. However, when I heard the names of the products, I started holding an interest in the person behind them. I originally believed an advisor was the one inventing the products, but after speaking to you, I’ve figured it out. It’s you, isn’t it? The one creating products using words from Earth,” Erica said, staring at Liselotte.

Liselotte cocked her head curiously. “What do you mean...?”

“You don’t need to act ignorant. No, let’s see. Don’t play dumb with me. My name’s Sakuraba Erika, but you... Is your name maybe Rikka? You look like a young girl in your teens, but how old are you on the inside? Do you get what I’m saying?” Erica suddenly dropped her polite, saintlike tone of speech and started speaking with familiarity, like a regular young woman her age.

“You really change the subject so suddenly. You’ve changed your tone now too. Is that your true way of speaking?” Liselotte asked in shock, eyes widened.

“I’d prefer you answer my question first. From now on, I’m not Saint Erica speaking, but Sakuraba Erika. Only if you don’t mind your maid listening in, that is.” Erica looked at Aria, who was standing behind Liselotte.

“I understand... In that case, I’m the one behind the Ricca Guild’s products. It’s fine if Aria remains here.”

After the first time, when Rio brought Miharu to her, she explained her previous life to Aria alone.

“Hmm. So, what’s your name and age? Are you Mrs. Rikka? Or Miss Rikka?”

“I’ve answered one question, so please answer my question next.” If Erica was going to say whatever she wanted, Liselotte had no reason to hold back any further.

“So the rule is for us to answer one question each. Fine. What did you wanna ask? Ah, my manner of speech, was it? This is my true self—no, this was my true self,” Erica said, answering Liselotte’s earlier question.

“Was?”

“It’s my turn next. What was your name in your past life?”

“Minamoto Rikka. What do you mean by ‘was’ your true self?”

“Sakuraba Erika is as good as dead... Right now I’m Saint Erica.” A shadow crossed Erica’s face for a moment, but she immediately covered it up with a smile.

“As good as dead?”

“My turn to ask. How old were you in your past life?”

“Sixteen.”

“Oh my, that’s rather young. I thought you were around the age of a university student, but you might just be older than me if you added up your total age. You still look like a child, so it’s pretty hard to believe.”

“Enough about my age. What did you mean by ‘good as dead’?” Liselotte asked next, not wanting to engage in idle chatter.

“Because I can no longer see my dearest lover anymore. He was everything to me. I have no intention of marrying anyone else, so I no longer feel any need to be Sakuraba Erika anymore. That’s why I became Saint Erica. However, talking to you has brought back some of those fond memories.”

It’s like I’ve returned just for this moment, Erica thought a little sadly.

“What should I ask next? Let’s see... Where did you live in Japan?”

“Bunkyo, Tokyo.”

“Ah ha ha. Seeing you say that with that face is funny. You lived in a good area, though. I was a lecturer at a university in Shinjuku, by the way.”

“Why did you assume I was reincarnated?”

“You’re talking to someone who was summoned to another world. I just figured it wouldn’t be a stretch for there to be reincarnated people as well. I read some light novels on the topic when I was in Japan too. So how did you die, Rikka?”

“...It was a bus accident,” Liselotte answered with a slightly unhappy look. Erica kept asking her questions that didn’t matter.

“Wow, how cliché.”

“It’s my turn next. Why are you asking such trivial things? I expected you to ask something more meaningful.”

“No reason in particular... I just didn’t want to ask Saint Erica’s questions as Sakuraba Erika. I said I was feeling nostalgic talking to you, didn’t I?” Erica’s smile turned strained for a moment, as though she had remembered some harsh reality.

“I see...”

Liselotte still wasn’t convinced. Her personality was so different to when she was a saint, it felt like she was talking to someone else.

“But you’re right. None of that matters. Let’s make the next question the last one.”

“All right.” There were still many things Liselotte wanted to ask, but she couldn’t force her to answer.

“Then I’ll go first.”

“Sure...” Liselotte braced herself for whatever question would come, but...

“Rikka—no, Liselotte. Do you have someone you love?”

“...Excuse me?” The question was so unexpected, she wasn’t sure she heard it right.

“Are you in love with anyone?”

“Is that something you need to know?”

“Yes. It’s standard girl gossip, isn’t it?”

“...I do not.”

“That’s a lie. You paused. Now, that won’t do... You have to answer honestly. Otherwise, I won’t answer your next question honestly either,” Erica said harshly.

“Honestly, I’m not sure. I’m too busy with work,” Liselotte answered somewhat shyly, eyes downcast.

“That reaction tells me there’s someone you’re interested in.”

“There’s someone who came to mind when you first asked, but...I cannot imagine us becoming lovers.”

“I see... But if there is someone, don’t do anything you’d regret. This is advice from a regretful past situation.”

“Okay...”

“Now it’s your turn, Liselotte.”

“Right.” Liselotte nodded, the question she wanted to ask already prepared. “Then...are you a hero? I only know of five heroes, as there’s been no information on the sixth...” Liselotte wondered.

“Hmm... You’re gonna ask that?” Erica seemed reluctant for some reason.

“Is there something wrong with that? I answered your question honestly, so you should answer mine too.” Liselotte suspected Erica was a hero already, but she wanted Erica to confirm it so it could be established as a fact.

“I don’t know if I should. You might be upset.”

“But I won’t know that until I hear the answer.”

“That’s true... Then I’ll answer. I’m a hero.”

Liselotte hummed at the satisfactory answer. “I see, so you really are one... But what’s so upsetting about that...?”

“Ah, how troubling indeed. I still need to keep the fact I’m a hero a secret, you see.” Erica suddenly started speaking in her saintlike tone.

“...Huh?” The sudden change left Liselotte taken aback.

“Oh!” Immediately after, Erica tried to grab at Liselotte. Before she knew it, Erica was right in front of her, leaving Liselotte in a state of shock.

“What do you think you’re doing?” Aria stood in front of Erica, grabbing her arm. She then proceeded to deftly hurl Erica’s body at the window; with a loud crash, the saint flew through the glass and fell to the ground.

“Wha...” Liselotte was left speechless at the sight.

“I shall apprehend her. The other attendant guards should be here soon. Stay over here, Lady Liselotte.”

With that, Aria drew the enchanted sword by her side and jumped out the window after Erica.

“Ah, how troubling. How troubling indeed.” Meanwhile, Erica was patting the dust off her dress without a single scratch on her.

That saint is a hero. Like Lady Satsuki, her Divine Arms strengthened her body and made her tougher. Killing a hero will only create a fuss... This is a problem... Aria sighed in annoyance.

“You’re not a normal attendant, are you?” Erica summoned her Divine Arms—a bishop’s staff—into her right hand as she questioned Aria.

“Of course not. None of Lady Liselotte’s attendants are normal attendants.”

“Heh. Heh heh heh. That’s lovely.”

No sooner had she said that than Erica charged at Aria. The powerful enhancement of her Divine Arms caused her speed to far surpass the limits of a normal human.

However, Aria’s physical body was also enhanced through her enchanted sword. She was able to react to Erica’s speed without a problem and close the distance between the saint and herself.

“Oh...” Erica’s eyes widened slightly in surprise. Whether it was to avoid a collision or increase the distance between them, she immediately moved to the right in a dramatic way.

But Aria soon closed that distance again, swinging her sword the moment she came within reach. She couldn’t afford to kill the hero, so she used the blunt side of her sword to strike. Erica raised her staff at the last minute to block that attack.

“Such wonderful strength indeed,” she murmured in awe, thrusting the staff forward to send Aria flying back.

Wh-What tremendous strength...

Aria’s body fell back heavily; she had lost in strength despite her enchanted sword’s power. Erica’s movement speed was still manageable, but her physical strength was on another level.

“It seems like your reinforcements are on their way. I should stop dawdling and clean this up quickly,” Erica said, switching to go on the offensive.

Using the reach of her staff, she inflicted her strikes on Aria from outside the reach of the sword.

The sixth hero seems to have a rather violent disposition.

Aria sometimes saw through the attacks and evaded them, and sometimes swung her sword to parry the staff off course, trying to close the gap to Erica. However, before Aria could come close, Erica thrust her staff into the ground with all her might. Immediately after, the ground rose up and formed a dirt wall, blocking Aria’s way.

“...”

Instead of pursuing her further, Aria retreated. She considered the possibility of Erica going after Liselotte and made sure to have the mansion to her back.

Soon after, the dirt wall Erica created blew up. Erica herself had swung her staff and mowed it down in annoyance. She faced Aria once again.

“You really are strong... I haven’t met anyone this strong before. It sure is a big world...” Erica spat out her words in great admiration.

“Your quick strength is superb, but it doesn’t seem like you’ve had combat training before.”

“Yes, you would be right.”

“Now that I have a grasp of your strength, I’m going to finish this now.”

“Hee hee hee. Who truly knows about that...” Erica dismissed Aria’s provocation with a smug laugh, then ran towards her, swinging her staff once more. The ground was scraped from left to right, sending a dusty shockwave towards Aria.

However, Aria instantly saw through the reach of the shockwave and retreated to a point where the shockwave was weakened. But the moment the shockwave eased, she made a rapid approach towards Erica.

“Uh!”

Erica’s reaction was delayed by her own dust cloud for a brief moment. She quickly tried to blow Aria away with another shockwave, raising her staff, but...

Too slow.

Aria sliced her sword at Erica’s staff before it could swing down, knocking it upwards. She then slipped right up to Erica and landed a heavy blow to her chest with the palm of her hand.

“Guh...”

It was one of the martial arts techniques she had learned from Rio at the Galarc Castle the other day. Erica’s body went flying through the air, sending her rolling ten meters away.

It definitely should have had an impact. Even with an enhanced body, she would’ve taken a considerable amount of damage. In reality, Erica was shaking on all fours, still conscious but seemingly unable to get up.

It’s over. The problem is how to restrain her... Perhaps I should land one more strike to knock her unconscious.

Though it was difficult, there was no helping it. The moment Aria reached a decision, she approached Erica and aimed a kick from below at her stomach.

“Gah...!”

Erica’s body jerked up, and several seconds later, gravity sent her falling back. This time, Erica seemed to lose consciousness, collapsing facedown without a twitch.

“Aria!”

At that moment, Natalie and Cosette came running out of the mansion. In their hands was a set of magic-sealing cuffs.

Thank goodness they’re so capable. If she’s restrained with those cuffs on, she should calm down a little.

Aria approached the facedown Erica. She leaned her weight on Erica’s back, pressing her into the ground.

“I’ll hold her down while you two put the cuffs... What?!”

Erica had flung Aria off her back with a sharp push-up. The momentum sent Aria flying ten meters or more.

No way. She didn’t receive any damage at all?!

Seeing Erica on her feet and full of life below her left Aria speechless. Erica casually looked upwards, met Aria’s eyes, and grinned eerily, then dashed at full speed away from her, towards the mansion.

“Cosette! Natalie! Stop that woman!” Aria was still falling through the air and gave her colleagues a quick order.

“Wha?!”

Before Cosette and Natalie could approach Erica, she had swung her bishop’s staff down towards the ground. The shockwave created was nothing like the one earlier—it was almost like a huge explosion had gone off, rumbling like thunder and sending a cloud of dust everywhere. Aria was unable to see the ground as she continued to fall.

Lady Liselotte...

She turned her gaze away from the dust cloud and towards the mansion. She could see Liselotte watching everything out of the second-floor window, and Erica running towards the mansion. Erica was looking around as though she were searching for Liselotte.

No... Hurry. Hurry and fall quicker.

The span of mere seconds felt like an eternity to Aria. When she finally reached the ground, she started running towards the mansion with all her might.

She couldn’t see anything past a meter ahead of her, but there was no time to be bothered by that. Praying that the guards would buy her enough time, Aria ran through the dust at full speed. Eventually, her vision cleared.

“Aria, no! Stay back!”

Liselotte’s familiar voice could be heard. At the same time, she spotted Erica waiting for her just a few meters away with her staff ready to swing down.

“There you are.”

Erica spotted Liselotte leaning out of the second-floor window to yell and grinned. At the same time, she finished swinging her staff down.

“Guh...”

And Aria’s vision was blacked out by the shockwave and dirt.

Interlude: Letter to the Centostella Kingdom

In the Centostella Kingdom, a few days after Rio and the others arrived in Yagumo...

Takahisa was holed up in his room as usual while Masato swung his sword around in the training area.. First Princess Lilianna’s knight, Hilda, was sparring with Masato that afternoon, teaching him how to refine his swordcraft. Aki was watching them practice from a distance.

While he still had a long way to go to catch up to Hilda, the career soldier and captain-ranked knight, Masato was improving every day. He was able to cross swords at a high level.

Over ten minutes had passed since they began sparring. Their matches didn’t end with a decisive exchange, continuing on endlessly by the participants resetting their positions. This meant they were panting rather heavily, out of breath.

“Breaks are important too. Let’s rest for a moment, Sir Masato.” Hilda halted in her movements, catching her breath. Masato stopped as well.

“Yes, Instructor Hilda,” Masato replied cheerfully, gasping for breath. He lowered his wooden training sword and wiped his sweat with a sigh.

“Your efforts are paying off today too.”

Lilianna, who had just arrived at the arena a short moment ago, approached the two. The reason why Hilda had called for the break was because she had seen her.

“Here you go, Sir Masato. Have a drink too.” Lilianna’s attendant, Frill, offered Masato a towel and drink.

“Oh, thank you, Frill... Phew, that hits the spot!” Masato thanked her warmly and drank. During that time, Aki also made her way over, quietly.

“Sir Masato, a letter arrived from the Galarc Kingdom.” Lilianna handed Masato a letter.

“Wait, really?! It must be from Satsuki.” Masato opened the letter happily. The sender was Satsuki, but Rio and Miharu also wrote messages whenever they were in Galarc. Masato cast his eyes over the letter in excitement while Aki stared at it in curiosity.

The letter reported on the recent situation of Satsuki and Rio. Rio had departed on another journey with the others, so this time the letter was written by Satsuki alone. She wrote about how they had fun living together in the mansion Rio received on the Galarc Castle grounds, about the bathtub there, and about the sleepover they had. There was also a message Rio and Miharu wanted to pass on to them. Finally, she wondered how Masato and Aki were doing.

“Huh, so Celia also went to that village... I wonder if Arslan’s doing well,” Masato mumbled to himself fondly as he read the letter. Once he reached the end, he noticed Aki’s gaze and offered her the letter.

“Here, you read it too. You’re curious, right?”

“You sure...?” Aki asked hesitantly. She figured the contents were directed at Masato alone. After what she and Takahisa did at the banquet, Miharu and Satsuki only kept in touch with Masato.

“I’m saying it’s fine, so it’s fine. They’re worried about you as well, you know?”

Go on, Masato urged with a wave of the letter.

“But...” Aki lifted her arm hesitantly, then immediately lowered it again.

“What’s wrong? Don’t you care about Miharu and Satsuki? There’s stuff written about Haruto too,” Masato encouraged.

“But after what I did...”

Aki was probably recalling what she had done to Miharu and Rio at Galarc as guilt plagued her expression. She didn’t have the right to read that letter, she thought.

“You’ve really reflected on it after all...”

“...” Aki ducked her head in silence. Ever since she came to Centostella, not a day had passed without her remembering what happened in Galarc. And every time she did, she was filled with gloom. Those feelings intensified every day.

But was that really a form of reflection? Aki didn’t have the confidence to say so. That’s why she couldn’t agree or disagree with Masato’s view.

“I wouldn’t show our brother this letter, but I think I can show you. So read it.”

“Why...?” Aki asked fearfully.

“Unlike Takahisa, you’ve actually reflected on it, and you regret what you did, right?”

“...” Masato kept saying words like ‘reflection’ and ‘regret,’ but Aki couldn’t agree with them. She remained silent—it was easy to call it reflection and regret, but so what? They were words that were only said when seeking forgiveness. Words used when seeking forgiveness, even though she was the one who was wrong.

Wasn’t that too convenient? She had done such a terrible thing... Wouldn’t it be too convenient to seek forgiveness after that? That was the question that filled Aki’s head.

That being said, she wasn’t so sure anymore. She definitely felt sorry for Miharu. She felt conflicted about Haruto, but she also felt guilty for that. She could accept that she had done something wrong.

But when she thought about Takahisa, she was also filled with a helpless emotion that she couldn’t put into words...

Aki really had no idea anymore. Her mind was all over the place. She wanted Miharu to conveniently appear and save her. And that in turn spurred on her guilty conscience further... She just couldn’t say she was reflecting on or regretting things.

Then, Lilianna looked at Aki.

Lady Aki has reflected on things and regretted them, which is causing her so much pain right now. In contrast, Sir Takahisa is...

She thought of Takahisa, who wasn’t present right now.

What’s done was done and would remain as a fact—there was no erasing that. That’s why Aki continued to suffer over it.

Takahisa was in similar pain, but he had shut himself in his room and refused to interact with anyone. When Lilianna compared the two, she just couldn’t see him suffering in the same way as Aki.

Time is needed to take a proper look at yourself. That’s what I believed, but...

Was that really the right thing to do? There was no telling if Takahisa reflected on what he did in Galarc and regretted it. Lilianna was starting to lose confidence.

“Well, whatever... I’ll leave this letter with you, Aki. You can decide when to read it for yourself. Here.”

Masato ran out of patience for the silent Aki and placed the letter in her hand.

“But...” Aki reflexively tried to push it back.

“Stop thinking so hard. You can just read it when you want to. How about you write what you’re feeling in a letter to Miharu? That’s another reason why I’d like you to read the letter, actually. I’ll give you the other letters as well.” Masato pushed the letter back firmly.

“...” Even after hearing that, Aki couldn’t read the letter right away. However, she didn’t try to return it to Masato anymore, and instead hugged it to her chest dearly.

Afterword

Hello everyone, this is Yuri Kitayama. Thank you for picking up Seirei Gensouki: Spirit Chronicles, volume 17, Saint’s Gospel.

So, we’ve finally reached volume 17. Normally, sales of earlier volumes tend to drop when a series comes this far, but the first wave of Spirit Chronicles continues to rise. It’s all thanks to you!

Thanks to your support, the third drama CD “Script with a Side of Heroine Ranking” has been included in the special edition of volume 17. To those of you who bought it, please enjoy the comical interaction between Rio and the heroines!

Next, and this has already been announced elsewhere, but two new pieces of Seirei Gensouki: Spirit Chronicles merchandise will be going on sale! There’s a body pillow cover of Professor Celia and Professor Celia’s perfume!

Body pillow aside, apparently it’s really rare to have perfume produced. I never thought I’d have a part in making perfume in my life, so it was a valuable experience. The body pillow cover of Professor Celia is so adorable, I just want to hug her tightly (there’s a version with her regular clothes in disarray, and a version in a swimsuit), and the perfume has a great scent as well. Please consider buying them if you’re interested!

The details of the body pillow and perfume have already been released, which you can find on the official sites for HJ Bunko and Melon Books, as well as my Twitter account (by the time this volume is released, preorders should be open).

Finally, I’d like to say a little something about the main story as well. Rio, Aria, and Aishia are teaming up for volume 18. The story is finally moving on to the next stage.

I’ll be able to talk about more details in the upcoming volumes regarding the saint’s surprising resilience and other things, so look forward to that alongside the story! (I’m so glad they got out of Yagumo in volume 7...!)

Seirei Gensouki: Spirit Chronicles, volume 18, Beast of the Land will be on sale this winter!

Let’s meet again in volume 18!

Yuri Kitayama

July 2020